Actions
Add a part
Add a parts entry
Add an associate
Add new associates, parts and history entries
Address
Associate
Associate and Supplier are mandatory
Associate is mandatory
Associate successfully created
Associate successfully deleted
Associate successfully purged
Associate successfully updated
Associates Manager
Associates Manager Configuration
Attribution Date
Attribution date is mandatory
Available rights:
Company
Configuration
Contact
Country
Create
Date of attribution
Date of end
Delete
Edit
Email
End Date
Manage plugin rights through GLPI profiles (Administration > Profiles)
Matricule (N° Insee)
Modify existing associates, parts and history
Name
Name is mandatory
New associate
New part
New parts history
No associate found
No parts history found
None
Number of parts
Number of parts is mandatory
Part
Part is mandatory
Person
Phone
Postal code
Profile
Read
Remove associates, parts and history
Rights
Rights Management
Supplier
Total
Total Value
Town
Type
Unit Value
Update
View associates, parts and history
